Guide to the Afro-American Cultural Center at Yale Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- African American Cultural Center records, Circa 1967-2001; Accession 2005-A-002
  - Posters
    - 1990s-2000s
      - People of Color Fighting Color in the Persian Gulf, 1991 January 1 (Box 17)
      - A Cabaret: Yale-Harvard Weekend, 1991 November 1 (Box 17)
      - Praise the Lord: Come Join Us for a Time of Worship and Praise, 1991 December 1 (Box 17)
      - An Evening with "In Progress" - A Concert, 1992 October 1 (Box 17)
      - Macbeth/ The Tragedy of Macbeth, 1992 October 1 (Box 17)
      - A Reception for Cast of "The Colored Museum", 1992 November 1 (Box 17)
      - Yale Repretory Theater News: The Colored Museum, 1992 November 1 (Box 17)
      - The Yale Round Table, 1992 November 1 (Box 17)
      - X=Empowerment: Malcolm X Conference [at SCSU], 1992 November 1 (Box 17)
      - The Minority Career Forum, New England, 1992 December 1 (Box 17)
      - House Party Z: Pajama Jam, 1993 January 1 (Box 17)
      - 1968-1993: 25, Yale School of Medicine Marks 25thAnniversary of MLK, Jr., 1993 January 1 (Box 17)
      - Martin Luther King Celebration, 1993 January 1 (Box 17)
      - The Yale Round Table, 1993 January 1 (Box 17)
      - A Night with Campos Parsi: A Recital, 1993 January 1 (Box 17)
      - Islam and the Pan-African Experience, 1993 November 1 (Box 17)
      - A Conversation with Shirley Taylor Haizlip, 1994 January 1 (Box 17)
      - Mali K.K. Ahmed, Dinner and Lecture, 1994 February 1 (Box 17)
      - The Continuing Presence of Blacks at Yale, 1995 March 4 (Box 17)
      - House Party, Opening Weekend, 1995 September 1 (Box 17)
      - The Spirit of Yale-Harvard: More than a Game, 1997 November 1 (Box 17)
      - Visions of Africa: Contemporary African Cinema, Circa 2000 (Box 17)
      - International Black Panther Film Festival, 2001 May 1 (Box 17)
  - Photos to be scanned and clippings (Box 18)
  - Publications (Box 19)
- Materials relating to the Afro-American Cultural Center at Yale, circa 1968-2004; Accession 2005-A-044
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2040
  - Founding of Afro-American/Black Studies - varied material, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Four black and white photographs of classmates, Circa 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous notes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Y4A proposal, memos, reports, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Y4A correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Armstead L. Robinson - papers, correspondence, eulogy, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, journals, and articles, 1969-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Event programs and brochures, 1982-1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Yale University minority recruitment, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Black Alumni Assoc. and Conference [not received], 1989, 1992-1993
  - AACC correspondence, 1983-1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AACC reports and bylaws, 1982-1983, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Varied correspondence/miscellaneous file, 1983-1990s, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Oral histories of the Afro-American Cultural Center at Yale, 2004; Accession 2005-A-067
  - Andrews, Dwight, 2004 October 12
    - Audiocassette (Box 1)
    - Videotape (Mini-DV) (Box 2)
  - Bertrand, Donald, 2004 October 26; 1 (Box 3)
  - Chiles, Nicholas, 2004 October 2; 1 (Box 4)
  - Collins, Roger L., Ph.D., 2004 October 2; 1 (Box 5)
    The materials are open for research.
  - Darnell, Michael, 2004 October 3; 1 (Box 6)
    Scope and Contents
    Recording on tape ends abruptly.
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 6U)
  - Foster, Craig, 2004 July 31
    - 2 audiocassettes (Box 9–10)
    - 2 videotapes (Mini-DV) (Box 7–8)
      Possible duplicates of audiocassettes (boxes 7-8).
  - Garrett, Nathan, 2004 October 2; 1 (Box 11)
  - Huggins, Paul, 2004 September 18
    - 3 videocassettes (Mini-DV) (Box 12–14)
      On the first videocassette (Box 12), the recording cuts out at 47:02 and resumes at 48:21.
    - 2 audiocassettes (Box 15–16)
    - Supporting materials, 2004 September 18 (Box 17)
  - Jackson, Onaje, 2004 October 2; 1 (Box 18)
  - Lawson, Joseph, 2004 October 2; 1 (Box 19)
  - Marshall, Charles Herbert, III, 2004 October 2; 1 (Box 20)
  - Moses, John R., 2004 October 2
    - Videotape (Mini-DV) (Box 21)
    - Audiocassette (Box 22)
  - Payne, Charles B., 2004 October 3; 2 (Box 23–24)
  - Pulley, Arthur L., 2004-09-22
    Permission required from interviewee for access to material during their lifetime, after which the materials will be open.
    - Audiocassette (Box 25)
    - Videotape (Mini-DV) (Box 26)
  - Pulley, Bernice Cosey, 2004-09-22
    - Audiocassette (Box 27)
    - Videotape (Mini-DV) (Box 28)
  - Pulley, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur L., 2004-09-22
    - Audiocassette (Box 29)
    - Videotape (Mini-DV) (Box 30)
  - Rhines, Jesse, 2004 October 3; 1 (Box 31)
  - Thompson, Robert Farris, 2004 September 17
    - Audiocassette (Box 32)
    - Videotape (Mini-DV) (Box 33)
  - Tree, Phoebe, 2004 October 2; 1
    Custodial History
    Audio cassette de-accessioned on 2016-03-28.
  - Turnipseed, Erica, 2004 October 2; 2 (Box 35–36)
  - Winters, Irving J., 2004 October 3; 1 (Box 37)
  - Woods, Allen, 2004 October 2; 2 (Box 38–39)
- Digitized photographs of individuals, activities and events [computer files], Circa 1960s-1990s; Accession 2005-A-190
  - [00001.tif], 1967 August; computer file (TIFF)
    General note
    Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
  - Eleanor Holmes Norton [00002.tif], 1960s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Panther Rally at courthouse [00003.tif], 1960s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00005.tif], 1960s; computer file (TIFF)
  - 4th from left Maureen Hunter '79, far right Rufus Nickens, M.Div. [00006.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - A Century of Blacks at Yale
    - Page 01-33 [00007.tif-00039.tif], 1970s; 33 computer files (TIFF)
    - Table of contents 1-3 [00040.tif-00042.tif], 1970s; 3 computer files (TIFF)
    - Title page [00043.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Bassist of Oliver Lake Quartet 1-2 [00044.tif-00045.tif], 1970s; 2 computer files (TIFF)
    - Ben Bates 1972 and Donald Forte 1979 [00046.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Bill Anderson [00047.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Black Law Students at AACC [00048.tif], 1974; computer file (TIFF)
  - Jim Alexander
    - 4th from left Maureen Hunter '79, far right Rufus Nickens, M.Div. [00049.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Walter Rodney [00050.tif-00051.tif], 1970s; 2 computer files (TIFF)
    - 4th from left Maureen Hunter '79, far right Rufus Nickens, M.Div. [00052.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Sonia Sanchez [00053.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Walter Rodney [00055.tif-00056.tif], 1970s; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Byron Rushing- SAY BROTHER [00057.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Cast of drama by Ben Healey '77 [00058.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Cecilia Baldwin, Khalid Lum, Barbara Picken, Valerie Scruggs, Alton Martin, no date, Lois Chapman, Darryl Nash [00059.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Charles Dutton and John Doolittle in Othello, photo by Paul J. Penders [00060.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Children on the Green [00061.tif], 1977 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Class of 1976 [00062.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Darryl Nash 1976, no date, Pam Price 1978, Lisa Chapman, Administrative Assistant [00063.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - David Crippens, host of SAY BROTHER[00064.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Diane McRoy, Khalid Lum, Macletus Dejoie [00065.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Divestment rally at Woodbridge [00066.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Donald Ogilvie [00067.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Drama by Ben Healey Jr, 77 [00068.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Dwight Andrew's Band, Jay Hoggard, Don Edwards [00069.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Dwight Andrews, Vienna Carroll 1977, Jay Hoggard [00070.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Event on the Green [00071.tif], 1977 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Faculty and students listen to president [00072.tif], 1974 November; computer file (TIFF)
  - Fay Burrell [00073.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Garfield Broussad '77, Khalid Lum, Claire Arlette Bunch '77 [00074.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Garfield Broussard, Byron Atkinson, Tommie Stan, Khalid Lum [00075.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Gospel Choir [00076.tif], 1977; computer file (TIFF)
  - Gospel Choir Rehearsal [00077.tif], 1977; computer file (TIFF)
  - Graduation [00078.tif-00079.tif], 1975; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Guitarist of Oliver Lake Quartet [00080.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Gulpillil, Bandilil, and Brian Syron on SAY BROTHER [00081.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Ian B Straker
    - Officers Lewis, A. and Charles, W. [00082.tif], 1977 August; computer file (TIFF)
    - photo by Ian B. Straker 1978 [00083.tif], computer file (TIFF)
    - Sam Owens 1978 with the Baker's Dozen [David Gibbons 6th from left] [00084.tif], computer file (TIFF)
  - Jay Hoggard and friend [00085.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Julian Bond [00086.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Khalid and students laughing on the steps [00087.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Khalid and students pose on house steps [00088.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Khalid and students pose outside of house [00089.tif-00091.tif], 1970s; 3 computer files (TIFF)
  - Khalid Lum and students racing up the steps of the house [00092.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Khalid Lum with an unidentified man [00093.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Khalid Lum with two unidentified persons [00094.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Khalid Lum with unidentified students [00095.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Khalid Lum [00096.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Khlaid Lum with unidentified students [00097.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Kika Ese drummers led by Paul Huggins, left [00098.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Kingman Brewster [00099.tif], 1975; computer file (TIFF)
  - l-r, Donald Watson, Bill Wright, Rudolph Green, Daria Israel, Cleveland Maire, Diane McRoy, Harold Morse, Macletus Dejoie, Kevin Allen, Raymond P. Moore [00100.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - l-r, Donald Watson, Bill Wright, Rudolph Green, Daria Israel, Cleveland Maire, Diane McRoy, Harold Morse, Macletus Dejoie, Kevin Allen, Raymond P. Moore [00101.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - l-r, Renee Baldwin, Khalid Lum, Barbara Pickens 1976, Valerie Scruggs 1976, Alton Martin 1976, Renee Lucrete 1977, Lois Chapman, Darryl Nash 1976 [Staff and Social Committee 1975-1976] [00102.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - l-r, Renee Baldwin, Khalid Lum, Debra Payne, Valerie Scruggs, Alton Martin, Lois Chapman, Barbara Pickins, Darryl Nash [Staff and Social Committee 1975-1976] [00103.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - l-r, Rudolph Green, Bill Wright, Cleveland Maire, Donald Watson, Kevin Allen, Macletus Dejoie, Harold Morse [00104.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Lenny Hinds [00106.tif], 1975 March 28; computer file (TIFF)
  - Lisa Pitt and unidentified woman [00107.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Lois Chapman, Khalid Lum, Alexis DeVeaux [00108.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Lois Chapman [l], Cecilia Baldwin [r] [00109.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Lois Chapman-administrative assistant [00110.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Macletus Dejoie [00111.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - March for Africa on New Haven streets [00112.tif], 1977 September 2; computer file (TIFF)
  - March for Africa on New Haven streets [00113.tif], 1977 September 3; computer file (TIFF)
  - March for Africa on New Haven streets [00114.tif], 1977 September 4; computer file (TIFF)
  - March for Africa on New Haven streets [00115.tif], 1977 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Michael Onaje Jackson 1977, low right [00116.tif], computer file (TIFF)
  - Michelle Harper, Effie G Harding [sitting], Teresa Banyard, Terrie House Lindsey [00117.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Nat Adderly Jr., 1977 and Phillip Street in a house-sponsored Dejavu concert [00118.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Niyomu Joamu Payton 1977 [00119.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - No. 43 Rudy Greene. 1975 [00120.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - No. 45 Don Martin, 1971 [00121.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - No.45 Don Martin, 1971, no.73 Earl Matory, ‘72 [00123.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - No.76 Ricky Lawrence, 1977 [00124.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Ntozake Shange reading at AACC gallery [00125.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Ntozake Shange with her cousin Khalid Lum [00126.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Nzinga dancers, 2 computer files (TIFF) [00127.tif-00128.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Oliver Lake Quartet [00129.tif-00138.tif], 1970s; 10 computer files (TIFF)
  - Oliver Lake [sax] and Paul Maddot [percussion] [00139.tif], 1977 February 4; computer file (TIFF)
  - Oliver Lake [00140.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Parents Day [00141.tif-00142.tif], 1975; 1 computer files (TIFF)
  - Paul Huggins- Kike Ese Drummer [00143.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Photo by Ian B. Striker 1978 [00144.tif], computer file (TIFF)
  - Photographic Illustrations
    - l-r, D. Watson, B. Wright, R. Green, D. Israel, C. Maire, D. McRoy, H. Morse, M. Dejoie, K. Allen, R.P. Moore [00145.tif], 1975; computer file (TIFF)
    - Barbara Pickens [00146.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Deon M. Hill chairs board meeting at center [00147.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Diane McRoy, Khalid Lum, Macletus Dejoie [00148.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Donald Ogilvie [00149.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Edith Jackson of Wall Street in Raisin in the Sun [00150.tif], 1977 August; computer file (TIFF)
    - El Hajj Malik [copyright] [00151.tif], 1977; computer file (TIFF)
    - El Hajj Malik, El Shabazz Afro-American Theatre Ensemble [copyright] [00152.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - El Hajj Malik [copyright] [00153.tif], 1977; computer file (TIFF)
    - faculty and students listen to president [00154.tif], 1974 November; computer file (TIFF)
    - Far right Dee Abdullah of El Hajj Malik [00155.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - "for colored girls…", at the house [00156.tif], 1976; computer file (TIFF)
    - "for colored girls who have considered suicide when the rainbow was enuf" [00157.tif], 1976; computer file (TIFF)
    - "for colored girls…" with Ntozake Shange, Trazana Beverly, Jamie Carlos [00158.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - "for colored girls…" with Oliver Lake on flute [00159.tif], 1976; computer file (TIFF)
    - Gospel Choir Rehearsal, Gent Lee Daniels, Director [00160.tif], 1977; computer file (TIFF)
    - Khalid Lum and unidentified man [00161.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Khalid Lum thinking [00162.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Khalid Lum [00163.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Kip Davis 2 of El Hajj Malik [00164.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Kip Davis of El Hajj Malik [copyright] [00165.tif], 1977; computer file (TIFF)
    - Macletus Dejoie [00166.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Masked actors from El Hajj Malik [00167.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Masked man from El Hajj Malik [copyright] [00168.tif], 1977; computer file (TIFF)
    - Michelle Harper, Effie G Harding [sitting], Teresa Banyard, Terrie House Lindsey [00169.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Niyomu Joamu Payton [00170.tif], 1977; computer file (TIFF)
    - Nzinga dancers, 2 computer files (TIFF) [00171.tif-00172.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Tom Connelly and Kip Davis of El Hajj Malik [copyright] [00174.tif], 1977; computer file (TIFF)
    - Unidentified gentlemen at Black Alumni Convocation (TIFF) [00175.tif-00176.tif], 1970s; 2 computer files (TIFF)
    - Actor from El Hajj Malik [copyright] [00177.tif-00178.tif], 1977; 2 computer files (TIFF)
    - Walter Rodney [00179.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Robert Stepto at Black Alumni Convocation [00180.tif-00181.tif], 1970s; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Roslayn Wilcox Bates 1976 [00182.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - SAY BROTHER, computer file (TIFF)
    - Al Gadsden [00183.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - An elderly Black woman [00184.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Byron Rushing- SAY BROTHER [00185.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - David Crippens host of [00186.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Gulpillil, Bandilil, and Brian Syron [00187.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Haki Madhubuti [00188.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Jim Cooper [00189.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Tom Sanders of the Celtics [00190.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Tony Brown [00191.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [00192.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Sonia Sanchez [00193.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Staff Marvin Blakely, Niyomu Payton, no date, uknown, no date, Donna Dinkins, Sonia Butler, no date, no date, Ken Penn, Ian Streaker, Phoebe Tree, K [00194.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Stokely Carmichael addresses students [00195.tif], 1978; computer file (TIFF)
  - Stokely Carmichael [00196.tif], 1978; computer file (TIFF)
  - Students at Ntozake gallery reading [00197.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Tom Sanders of the Celtics- SAY BROTHER [00199.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Toni Morrison [00200.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Tyra Lopes, James Rawls in game room tournament [00201.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Unidentified gentlemen at Black Alumni Convocation [00202.tif-00203.tif], Undated; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Ben Helley [00204.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Woman and Khalid Lum in front of Center [00205.tif], 1977 August; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled from SAY BROTHER [00206.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Valerie Scruggs '76, Barbara Picken '76, Darryl Nash '76, Deborah Payne '76, Alton Martin '76 [00207.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Voices of East Harlem [00208.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Walter Rodney and Bill Anderson [00209.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Walter Rodney [00210.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Yale Gospel Choir [00211.tif-00212.tif], Undated; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Yonkers Yanohe Theatre at Lee High School [00213.tif], 1976 October; computer file (TIFF)
  - Alma Beck
    - Untitled [00214.tif-00217.tif], 1970s; 4 computer files (TIFF)
  - Jim Alexander
    - Untitled [00218.tif-00233.tif], 1970s; 16
  - Photographic Illustrations
    - Untitled [00234.tif-00260.tif], 1970s; 26 computer files (TIFF)
    - Untitled-063 [copyright] [00261.tif], 1970s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [00262.tif-00268.tif], 1970s; 7 computer files (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00269.tif-00311.tif], 1970s; 43 computer files (TIFF)
  - Untitled-073 [00312.tif], 1977 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-074 [00313.tif], 1977 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-075 [00314.tif], 1977 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-076 [00315.tif], 1975 April; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00316.tif-00334.tif], 1970s; 19 computer files (TIFF)
  - Untitled-170 [00335.tif], 1977 August; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00336.tif-00347.tif], 1970s; 12 computer files (TIFF)
  - 1985 P. Bailey, T. Thornton, D. Fossett, K. Clark, Sheila, Julie, Dorena, Jometric, K. Desouza, E. Welcome, P. Bailey T. Lopes, W. Hodges, M. White, S. Long [00348.tif], computer file (TIFF)
  - Alphonso Pinkney, newspaper [00349.tif], 1986 January 21; computer file (TIFF)
  - Amy Jordan 1988, Maxim Thorne 1989 at the Manny Marable Reception [00350.tif], 1987 March; computer file (TIFF)
  - Angela Bassett 1980,YSD 1983 [left], L. Scott Caldwell [right] cast of Joe Turner reception [00351.tif], 1986; computer file (TIFF)
  - Annual reception [00352.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Apartheid painting by Johnnie Gates [00353.tif], 1987; computer file (TIFF)
  - Arts, Crafts, and Book Fair [00354.tif-00355.tif, 1987; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Bart, Byron Taylor 1987, Chad 1987, Kenny Wheeler 1987, Ricky Ewing 1987 [00356.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Black Arts and Crafts Fair [00357.tif-00359.tif], 1980s; 4 computer files (TIFF)
  - Bronze 2 by Hugh Harrell [00361.tif-00363.tif], 1980s; 3 computer files (TIFF)
  - Caroline Jackson and an unidentified man [00364.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Caroline Jackson and an unidentified woman [00365.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Caroline Jackson dancing [00366.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Caroline Jackson discusses the Norma Holt photo exhibit with high school students [00367.tif], 1987 February; computer file (TIFF)
  - Caroline Jackson [00368.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Charles Dutton [00369.tif-00370.tif], 1980s; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Charles Dutton as Levee in "Ma Rainey…" [00371.tif], 1983; computer file (TIFF)
  - Charles Dutton - head shot [00372.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Charles Dutton [00373.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Charles Martin
    - Beverly Smith-Dawson Drama [00374.tif], 1988; computer file (TIFF)
    - Charles Martin self portrait [00375.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
    - David Mills and Kimberly Clayton in the apartment [00376.tif], 1988; computer file (TIFF)
  - Cheryl Contu [00377.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Class of 1980 [00378.tif], computer file (TIFF)
  - Class of 1981 [00379.tif], computer file (TIFF)
  - Curtis Etherley, Michelle Pindar, Joe Turner cast reception [00380.tif], 1986; computer file (TIFF)
  - Desiree Wocks 1990, Dionsijia 1989 [00381.tif-00382.tif], 1987 March; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Diane Johnson at BGn Evening of Jazz and Lit. also featuring Dwight Andrews and Gloria Naylor [00383.tif], 1982; computer file (TIFF)
  - Dianne Turner, right [00384.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Doris Davis, Director of Minority Recruiting at Yale, and Thomas Dudeck, Educational Services Manager at United Illuminating addressing high school students [00385.tif], 1987 February; computer file (TIFF)
  - Emily Hooper 1988 [left], Kimberly Scott [right], Joe Turner Cast Reception [00386.tif], 1986 Fall; computer file (TIFF)
  - Emily Hooper 1988, Sheila Ducksworth 1989, Kim Barker 1989 [00387.tif], 1987 March; computer file (TIFF)
  - Emily Reeves, Jackie, no date, Emily Hooper 1988, Kim Barker 1989 [00388.tif], 1987 March; computer file (TIFF)
  - Game room tournament [00389.tif-00391.tif], 1986; 3 computer files (TIFF)
  - Gary Franks, 1975 [00392.tif], 1987 March; computer file (TIFF)
  - Glasser King Day [00393.tif], 1985; computer file (TIFF)
  - Grant Little [00394.tif], 1987; computer file (TIFF)
  - Greeks [00395.tif-00396.tif], 1980s; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Harvard Yale weekend [00397.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Henry Porter [00398.tif-00399.tif], 1980s; 2 computer filed (TIFF)
  - Hillhouse sophomore Ata-Ul-Aziz-Hamed shows students where he was born [00400.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - HYC [00401.tif-00402.tif], 1987; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Ian Straker, M. Div. 1985 BCAY [00403.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Ian Striker, M.Div. 1985 [00404.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Judith Oriole 1989 [00405.tif], 1985; computer file (TIFF)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi- Black Male Leadership Speaker Series, 18 computer files (TIFF) [00406.tif-00423.tif], 1987; computer file (TIFF)
  - Karen Stewart 1988 [00424.tif], 1987 March; computer file (TIFF)
  - Kate Robinson, Wayne Grant, Jennifer Lok, Harold Little, Caroline Jackson, Thomas Dudeck [00425.tif], 1987 February; computer file (TIFF)